It's midday already?
Did I catch a cold or something?
My body does feel kinda sluggish.
Were my hands always this small?
Something's definitely off.
My head feels kinda funny, too.
Huh?!
Animal Friends
KonoMia: God's Blessing
on This Magnificent World
Hang on, hang on. Pull it together.
I'm Mahiro Oyama,
an avid eroge gamer and self-sufficient
home security officer.
I'm supposed to be a young man in his prime.
Th-This is crazy, but...
I think I've turned into a girl!
Shut-in
B-Better check.
You know? For science.
Morning, Onii-chan!
W-Wait, I swear I wasn't—
I mean— Uh— I...
Yup. Looks like that did the trick.
I gotta say though, Onii-chan...
I didn’t expect you to
turn out looking so cute.
Around the same age as a
middle-schooler, perhaps?
M-Mihari...
You didn't drug me, did you?!
Just a little drop in your drink.
Y-You can't just treat people like guinea pigs!
What do you take your big
brother for, anyway?
An unemployed, good-for-nothing shut-in.
Unemployed
A nocturnal deadweight who hasn't
left the house in two years.
Shut-in
Not to mention, you're addicted
to those gross video games.
Gross
I think it's about time you got a job.
But how can I find work looking like this?
You want me to sell my body?
Absolutely not!
I just need you to let me monitor you.
Think of it like a clinical trial.
And don't worry.
You should go back to normal once
you stop taking the medicine.
...I think.
Y-You think?!
Well, what's done is done.
Why don't you try enjoying
life as a girl for a bit?
As a girl?
That being said, though,
you could start by getting up a little earlier
and adopting a healthier lifestyle.
All right, you want me to enjoy myself?
Then I'll indulge in the greatest
pleasure life has to offer!
Girl edition!
Well, you know where the door is. Scram!
You shouldn't even be barging
into my room in the first place.
Ew...
Oh, Onii-chan.
Let me let you in on a little secret.
Hmm?
Apparently, the female orgasm, right?
It's 100 times more
intense than the male's.
Huh?
I'm just saying, if you rush into
this before you're ready...
The experience might quite
literally blow your mind.
Huh?
Kaboom!
You're a scoundrel!
ONIMAI: I'm Now Your Sister
Mahiro Oyama
Mihari Oyama
ONIMAI: I'm Now Your Sister
ONIMAI
Onimai.
Mahiro
#01 Mahiro's Confusing New Body
Girl, boy. It doesn’t matter.
I'm still a machine!
A monster-slaying machine!
Ugh, but the boss is gonna
spawn any moment now.
Tea
I gotta do it. For the game.
Nope, not happening!
Oh, whoops. Um...
Oh, right!
All right, Onii-chan.
Show me your tummy.
I'd rather not do that sort of
roleplaying with my little sister...
I'm doing a check-up!
Now, breathe in.
And out.
Do we have to do this every day?
For the time being.
Okay, now turn around.
Onii-chan...
Hmm?
It smells like wet dog in here.
Uh...
When was the last time you bathed?
U-Um...
Like five days ago?
So the time has finally come...
I'm sorry!
Wait— Who am I apologizing to?!
Have I lost it?!
All right.
Gotta make sure I don't overstimulate myself.
It's actually... more lewd this way.
Onii-chan, I'm leaving a change
of clothes out here, okay?
Wh-What was that?!
Are you okay?!
I-I'm fine!
What's gotten into me today?
There's nothing much to
speak of there, anyway.
I guess taking a bath doesn't
hurt every once in a while.
Now, where did she put my clothes?
Ugh, Mihari must have left her own
clothes here instead of mine.
Hey! What about my clothes?!
I told you! I left them right there!
You serious...?
ONIMAI
Onimai.
So incredibly cuteeeee!
I've always wanted a little
sister to play dress-up with!
I'm not your little sister!
Oh, good! You didn't skip the underwear.
Um, is this going to be a regular thing?
I don't feel right wearing
such revealing clothes.
I'm getting changed right
after this, you hear?
Oh yeah, that reminds me.
I went ahead and put away all
your old clothes for you.
I'll be arranging all your
outfits from now on, okay?
Huh?!
I mean, come on.
If I left you to your own devices,
you'd never get changed.
Getting up and getting
dressed in the morning...
Remembering to wash your
face and eat breakfast...
Taking a bath every day and
brushing your teeth before bed...
It's important in life to maintain
a well-balanced routine.
Besides,
your old clothes probably don't
fit you anymore anyway, right?
And plus...
Look at you.
You're so much cuter now.
Might as well dress up
and show off a little.
Y-Yeah...
Teehee.
Nope! No, no, no!
I'm not into that stuff!
Wearing dainty clothes like
this just weirds me out.
All right, then.
You wanna try something a
little more conservative?
W-Well, maybe just this once...
I think I can put up with it.
Here's your outfit for today
Mihari
Hmm...
ONIMAI
Onimai.
What's the matter, Onii-chan?
What's gotten you down this time?
I've reached my breaking point, Mihari.
I don't think I can stand the
no-fap life much longer.
I was desperate to suppress the urge,
so I tried playing the BL game
I accidentally bought once, but...
Toppington
I'll make it so that you'll never be able to forget me.
I'll leave my mark on you,
so everyone will know you're mine.
I'll make it so that you'll
never be able to forget me.
I'll leave my mark on you,
so everyone will know you're mine.
Bottomsley
No, stop!
I'm not...
I got a little turned on.
I never thought this day would come...
I-It's okay.
You're a girl now, after all.
It might just come with
the territory, you know?
I refuse to accept this!
Honestly...
I wonder if the treatment has
begun to alter his tastes.
I'm pretty sure he likes the girly
outfits more than he lets on as well.
Officer Busted
Anime Sports Edition
Hey, Onii-chan.
Hmm?
If you're up for it,
I know just the thing that'll
help clear your head.
Noooo way!
Not in a million years!
You know I hate exercising!
Do you even understand what it means
to be a home security officer?!
Stop saying that like it's a badge of honor!
I said I don't want to...!
Stop wriggling.
It'll help clear your head, won't it?
You can't make me! I'm not ready to die!
Then you'd rather fall
further into that BL rabbit hole?
I can't believe I'm stepping outside for the
first time in two years because of this.
All right, Onii-chan.
You'll feel much better once
you get your body moving.
Onii-chan?
W-Will you at least... stick beside me?
Of course. I planned on doing
so from the get-go, okay?
Okay.
I'm starting to wonder who's
really the younger sister here.
Wai— Hold up— Mihari!
You're going too fast!
Oh, sorry!
You must have gotten a little out of shape.
In more ways than one.
Even if I were in shape...
I wouldn't be able to keep up with you.
My little sister is a talented person.
You might even say too talented.
She's always been athletic.
She was even setting track
records back in middle school.
Highest Scoring Students in the First Semester Finals
1 Mihari Oyama 500 points
She was so good at school
that she even got accepted to
college several years early.
I was nothing compared to such
a high-achieving little sister,
and people would judge me
relentlessly because of it.
Not that that was their
sole reason for doing so.
And look at me now, my own
little sister's guinea pig.
But, strangely enough,
I think I'm okay with it.
It feels like I've found a
role I can actually thrive in.
Maybe it's time I give up trying
to be the older brother,
and stay as I am now...
Onii-chan?
What's wrong?
It hurts.
What does?
My nipples.
Why aren't you wearing it?!
Didn't I give you one?!
Well, uh...
It was too much. I had to
draw the line somewhere.
You know?
Say no more.
You and I are going bra shopping.
Right now.
What?
H-Hey! I said I'm fine!
No complaining.
Hi, welcome in!
Excuse me. This is her first time.
Would you mind showing her the ropes?
Absolutely. Right this way.
Okey-doke.
I'm going to start measuring, all right?
It'll only take a second.
W-Wai—!
No need to feel embarrassed.
Every girl has to wear one eventually.
Let's see...
I think you're around this size.
Which one would you like?
How about we try this one on
and see how you feel?
You can always clasp it on
back-to-front and then swivel it around.
Mhmm, mhmm.
Wow, so you went with the sports bra?
It really suits you.
I think I'm having an identity crisis!
Hey.
Come on, what happened to exercising?
I'm done.
Two steps forward, one step back, I suppose.
Now then, I wonder what's
in store for us next...
The Big Brother
Rehabilitation Project
See you
next time
Next Episode: Mahiro and the Girl's Day Out
Illustration: Yusuke Matsuo
See you next time!