Oyama
Th—
Practice Questions
They're all solved...
How?! How did you do that?!
Eh? A-aaahhh, um...
W-while I was absent from school,
Onee-chan went and tutored me...
I see... Your Onee-san
is a doctor, after all.
Hm?
Mahiro
Heeere! I've brought some refreshments!
Thank you very much!
Doing your homework? Nice going!
Yep! Our finals start next week, after all.
Ooh, black tea! What a nice scent!
Right? Help yourself to
some cookies alongside it.
Thanks for the snack!
Math is just the worst...
"x" and whatnot keep showing up...
Ah...
For instance, take this question here...
"x" is the cost of an orange, correct?
When you think about it, it's just
middle-school homework...
It's been a while, but something like
this should be a piece of cake...
So this is the equation here...
Which means we can take this
number and carry it over here...
At this rate...
Okay...
I might just wind up
untouchable in terms of exams!
Now, add those two together.
Then you just divide!
Oh, I get it now!
(Woo-HOO!)
It's there? It's gone?!
(It's gone?!)
Absent? Present!
(Present!)
Affixed, Guess I'm fixed?
Huh? Which one is it?! Trance, trance, trance!
It's dair? It's nought!
(It's nought!)
ONIMAI: Onii-chan is Done For!
AbSENT? pRE:sent!
(pRE:sent!)
ONIMAI: Onii-chan is Done For!
The Why of [I], erodes!
Mahiro Oyama
Farewell to UV light, indoor guard at the ready!
Bye-bye, alright! Best to stay inside all day!
That will of mine's up and done willed itself away!
Mihari Oyama
Fight, flight, out like a light! Back to my home I go!
Aah, a world unknown,
it met with my gaze and flashed a smile
It pulls me in, this may just be worth my whiiile
Hey, check it out,
this water's as sweet as paradise!
Fashion, to make-up, hairstyles et al,
Within the garden of maidens, dancing takes bloom!
Wha, madame? Who's that? Guy's the I, no lie!
(Who!)
(Are!)
(It's me!)
I don't know what's happening, my fragile identity
Begins anew right now, a sense of wonder!
(Woo-HOO!)
At this rate, maybe my very psyche will fade and melt!
Now arise! Heed my call! Go forth, pillar of self!
(Hey!)
(Pillar of self!)
Let's edge our best, so we can see a happy end!
It's there? It's gone?!
(It's gone?!)
Absent? Present!
(Present!)
Affixed, guess I'm fixed?
Huh? Which one is it?! Trance, trance, trance!
ONIMAI: Onii-chan is Done For!
It's dair? It's nought!
(It's nought!)
AbSENT? pRE:sent!
(pRE:sent!)
The Why of [I]-dentity, will crumble forth!
#07 Mahiro and RPGs
Haaahh... I hate tests.
Must be nice, Mahiro-chan.
Being so calm about this!
I wonder...!?
It's Asahi and Miyo-chan!
Good morning!
The ever-upbeat Asahi's
fallen down into the dumps...!
Tests are her natural enemy after all.
Ah, another victim of our
test-score-obsessed society...
It's like I'm looking at my past self...
There, there. You poor thing...!
I know exactly how you feel...!
Mahiron! Let's both take on those
supplementary classes together, okay!?
Eh?! Me too?!
Don't you think you're being a little hasty?!
You sure it's fine not to separate them?
Well, Asahi's at rock bottom...
We've got this, okay?!
I'll let her borrow Mahiro-chan for today.
I don't think I've ever felt this
calm before an exam in my life...
Math
Social Studies
Science
Then, you may begin.
Answer Sheet
A perfect score would be too risky.
I'll make some mistakes.
All things in moderation!
That girl's always asleep, isn't she...
Today's definitely not the day for that, though...
Poke, poke.
I understand how she feels.
These seats are so
warm, aren't they...!
All right, that's it.
Pass your answer sheets
back to front, please!
Mueh...?
GYEEEHHH!!
I-It's over...
All right!
I'll turn it all around with the next one!
Math
Social
Studies
Science
Japanese
English
Huh? Which era?
Vegetation...? ......s-stratum?!
Gueeehhh, I forgot all about
classical literatureee...!
Ah!
English, THAT I can do!
Well then, I'll be handing
back your tests now.
Abahhh...
Mahiro-chan?
H-huh—?!
I knew I could count on you, Mahiron!
Let's do our best in those
supplementary lessons together!
I'll help too!
I'll tutor you!
But, I'm kinda relieved somehow.
Mahiro-chan, you seem
more like yourself this way.
I see now...
Ehhh? Mahiro-chan, you slept through math?
She's a good-for-nothing, after all!
That's just like Mahiro-chan though, isn't it?
So true!
There was no need
to take it so seriously...
What are we gonna do with you?
T-these really are a bit too...
"Good-for-nothing" is fine and all, but...
Messing up in subjects based around
memorization is a bit frustrating...!
Gaming forbidden!
Guess I'll have to brush up
on a few things after all...
Onii-chan...
I'll go ahead and increase your allowance a tad.
Eh?! Mihari-sama, my patron deity...!
Onimai...
ONIMAI
Momiji! Lemme copy your notes from the lesson!
Did you fall asleep again?
By the way, I'm "Mahiron", and Miyo-chan's "Miyochin"...
Does Momiji not have a
nickname you call her by?
Now that you mention it, you're right.
Oh, yeah.
Miyo-chan went to a different
elementary school, after all.
I did call her something else!
Back in elementary, anyways.
It was embarrassing, so I asked her to quit it.
Eeehhhh~? Now you've got us curious!
That name was...
"Momijiro"!
Momijiro...?
Momi
jiro
It kinda suits her.
It's 'cause I thought
she was a boy at first.
I know what you mean!
Come onnn...!
Japanese 1
Glayglay
ATK Magic
Fire
Lightning
Defense
Lost Quest 9 Strat Notes!
Hero
OneH Weapons  TwoH Weapons
Greatswords
ATK Magic
Lost Quest 9 Strat Notes!
Greatswords
OneH Weapons  TwoH Weapons
Lost Quest 9 Strat Notes!
Greatswords
OneH Weapons  TwoH W
OneH Weapons  TwoH Weap
Lost Quest 9 Strat Notes!
OneH Weapons  TwoH Weapons
Skill coherency is
gonna be crucial.
First off, I gotta awaken
the hero, though...!
Hmmm... power or speed, I wonder...
Japanese 1
I wanna get home and
play more right away...!
Hm?
I wonder if Mahiro-chan
needs to go to the bathroom?
Sensei! Can we use the
restroom for a moment?
Go ahead!
H-huh...!?
Jeez!
You're so hard to read, Mahiro-chan!
Ahh... sorry, sorry!
I just wanted get back home
already and continue my game!
Y'know, the one that just came
out yesterday, Lost Quest IX!
It's the new entry we've all
been waiting so long for...!
That so...!
Sorry... I'm not too acquainted with it.
What?! You don't know the Lost Quest?!
Asahi knows it!
Oooh?!
Lost Quest, my 'nii-chan's played those!
Ah, you've got an
Onii-san, don't you...
Boys sure do love video games.
Right?
That's right...
Everyone here's a girl, after all...
What do girls even talk about normally?
Huh?
Er, uhhhh...
Now that you ask...
Don't overthink it, it's just fine
to chat about whatever you want!
When you're talking about games, Mahiron,
you look like you're having so much fun, it's adorable!
Asahi...
You really are such a good girl!
Theeere, there, there...!
I-I-I...
I think so toooooo!
Though, if we're discussing what girls like to
talk about, it's gotta be gossiping about love!
When it's coming from Miyo-chan, I think you
might interpret that stuff a little differently...
Eeeeehhh!?
Everybody's so kind and mindful...!
When we talk again, I'll have
to let 'em know all about it!
Truthfully, I'd like to have a deeper
discussion about this stuff,
but that'd be asking for too much.
How far did you get?
Right now, I've just gotten
out of the port town or so...
Could you guys be talking about Lost Quest?!
U-Um... Oyama, right?
You play Lost Quest?
Absolutely, absolutely!
Of course I do!
Ah, sorry for kinda butting in there so suddenly.
It's okay, we don't mind...
Right?
Y-Yeah, of course not.
T-then, which companion did you recruit first?
I got, y'know, that
one with the funny name...
Could you mean Glayglay?!
Y-Yeah...
Really?! Me too!
B-but, his defense is a bit...
It's real low, isn't it?
True, true!
That reminds me!
You know that enemy you encounter
in the first dungeon?
I got some serious chills from that thing!
It really is so much easier
to talk with other guys!
Thank goodness I've got you
all to talk to about this!
Ah! Which entry in the
series is your favorite?
It's gotta be six, right? Six!
Eh? Six?
Sorry, I haven't played that one.
Whaaat? You secondary...!
I mean, it came out before
I was born, you know?
Before I was born...
Before I was born, you know?
Before I was born
B-B-Before you were... born?
What's wrong, Mahiro-chan?!
Ah, er...
It's nothing...
The boys made her cry!
You're the worst!
Eh?!
Ah!
Sorry about earlier!
Oyama's sure nice, huh...?
Yeah...
Mahiro has leveled up!
ONIMAI
Onimai.
Home Ec Room
Isn't it great when we get days
with more practical classes?
Y'got that right!
All right,
next week, it's time for the cooking class
that you've all been waiting for!
We'll be baking cookies!
The school will provide all
the basic ingredients,
so if you'd like for yours to be special,
discuss it with your group
and bring in the necessary
extra ingredients, if you please!
Woohoooooo!
To think that we get to
eat sweets at school!
Perks and bonuses abound!
We have to make them, though.
Right...
Hey, hey, what kind of
cookies should we bake?
Miyo-chan, are you good at baking sweets?
I love making things!
Ehhh~ We'll work
together perfectly!
I love eating said things!
Our team's gonna do just fine!
Mahiro-chan...
Hm?
I'm sorry, but I wouldn't
get your hopes up just yet.
She might look the part,
but her baking's terrible.
Is that... so...
I wonder what kind of cookies we should make...!
If we leave her unchecked,
it'll be a disaster!
I don't wanna make her feel bad, though.
Let's make sure we catch and
correct her mistakes discreetly.
Yeah...
So, can you two bake sweets, then?
What should we do about
making those cookies?
I'm sure we could just ask Mihari for help,
but her teaching technique is a little...
Sweets are a science, you know?!
Making sweets should be more like...
"Fluffy!", "Happy!", that
sorta thing, you know?
S-so cute...
Oh, in that case, why don't we head to my place
together and have my Onee-chan teach us?
That's it!
I'm home!
Onee-chan, are you home yet?
Heeeeere~!
It's your Onee-chan...!
Help me up...!
S-shoot, Mahiro-chan!?
Hey! You should let me know
before you bring people over!
It's embarrassing to be seen like this...
And this is how she looks
when she's let her guard down.
A whole new variant!
How to make cookies, you ask?
We're gonna be making
them in class next week.
We wanted to try and
deviate from the basic recipe.
In that case, leave it all to your Onee-san!
You two are gonna get my full, intricate
course, down to the very, last, touch!
That's our Kaede-chan!
It's even vaguely lewd...!
I gotta redeem myself somehow!
Roufl
Truth be told...
I've always dreamed of making
sweets with my little sister.
Ehh? You could've told me!
There wouldn't be any point if I
forced you into it, would there?
Oh, am I getting in the way?
Not at all.
Mahiro-chan's my little sister too!
Now that I'm thinking about it, I taught
Mihari the same way all those years ago.
She would've been right around
Mahiro-chan's age at the time.
She was so excited to make
cookies for her Onii-san.
Now that you mention it,
I do remember her baking
cookies at home a lot back then...
She was just giving us some at your
place the other day too, Mahiro-chan.
I'm sure they were delicious...!
They say the secret
ingredient is love, you know?
Thinking of the one you're making food for
might just be the trick to baking!
The one you're making food for... huh...
Did we all decide on a variety?
Yup!
The results are in, and the flavor
of choice is black tea!
Black tea, huh?
All you have to do is add in tea leaves.
Sure, sure! Sounds fancy,
I think it's a great idea!
Roufl
Let's get started, then.
First, add the sugar and eggs
to a bowl of melted butter.
Then mix well before adding the flour.
Mixing!
Now, add the tea leaves.
Adding!
Gently combine...
Combining!
Once cooled, roll out the batter, and...
Now, it's finally time
to cut out the cookies!
Miyo-chan?!
Safe...
I've got the cookie cutters here.
Thank you!
We were just about to have some
huge cookies on our hands...
Even though she nailed all the instructions...
Now all that's left is to bake them!
All done!
Woaahhh!
They even seem edible!
We didn't burn them either!
I think we did it!
They look really good, too!
Thank goodness...!
How did it go, then?
Sensei, why don't you try one yourself?
M-Murosaki-san's group, right?
Ara~!
You've just gotta have 'em
be hand-made, y'know!
Nah, Miyochin's own
cooking is a total...
They sure are tasty, right, Asahi?!
Tasty...
Here, try another one, Miyo-chan!
So good!
Right?
Delicious, right?
Welcome home!
Congrats on making it through another hard day!
Here. These are for you.
What are they? Cookies?
Black tea flavored cookies.
You like black tea, don't you?
Yeah...
I do.
We...
We made them in Home Ec today.
Onii-chan, you made these?!
They're not anywhere near as
good as yours, though, okay?!
Now, here we go...
Come on...!
It'd be such a waste to eat
something like this...!
The scent of Earl Grey...
They're delicious...
O-K, 1•2•3's our cue, hey~
Ehehe!
Come on! To the secret garden and away!
(Wooooo...!)
Onii—...Mahiro-chan, how about a maid outfit today?
No no, it's gotta be a bunnygirl suit, right?
Eh?
How about we try a pair of matching Hakamas!
E-err, um...!
Hey! Hold on!
Well either way, strip 'em off!
No, stooooooop!
Genius at the grind, subject has resigned
(From dusk to dawn~)
Drug status: It's a huge • suc • cess!
(Hold on, hold on!)
Cute gal acquired, now time to caress!
(Well now, go on~)
My pal's rewired, oh-ho yes!
(Snicker, snicker!)
Let's party woo-hoo, yay, yay, yay!
(Ain't that a black sheep within the girls' garden!?)
Adventure and yuri yuri bloomin' all night!
(Emotions all mixed up!)
O-K, 1•2•3's our cue, hey~
We've passed the ♂gender♀ borderline!
Ba-dump ba-dump, to the you
venturing to a new world:
Here we goooo!
(One!)
(Two!)
(Three!)
(Go Beyond World!)
(Woooo!)
W-w-w-well, whatever! That's just fine!
(W-woo!)
You win! I give up!
(Wooooo, yeah yeah!)
A girl's itty body holds oh so many
BIG ol' secrets yes indeed!
(Yeah! Yeah! Wooo!)
All one's might! Here's some fight!
(W-woo!)
Why, we may have quuuite the slight?
(Woooooo, yeah yeah!)
They say girl power, hey, is what makes the world go 'rooound!
(Yeah! Yeah! Yaaaaaay!)
(Nananana, nanana, nanana~)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
To my nigh Identity Cry-sis:
I'll see you again, some day!
Next Episode: Mahiro's First Girls-only Sleepover
Illustration: Yoshimichi Kameda
See you next time!